// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "java.util.Collections is a",
    answer: "A. Class",
    options: [
      "A. Class",
      "B. Interface",
      "c. Object",
      "D. None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "LinkedList implements?",
    answer: "C. Both A and B",
    options: [
      "A. List",
      "B. Deque",
      "C. Both A and B",
      "D. None of the above"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of those doesnâ€™t have an index based structure?",
    answer: "B. set",
    options: [
      "A. List",
      "B. set",
      "C. Map",
      "D. None of the above."
      
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "In which case, a program is expected to recover?",
    answer: "B. If an exception occurs.",
    options: [
      "A. If an error accours",
      "B. If an exception occurs.",
      "C. Both of the above.",
      "D. None of the above."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What will happen if static modifier is removed from the signature of the main method?",
    answer: "D. RunTime Error: NoSuchMethodError.",
    options: [
      "A. Program compiles and gives an Output.",
      "B. Program will compile and run without any output.",
      "C. Compilation error.",
      "D. RunTime Error: NoSuchMethodError."
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What does XML stand for?",
    answer: "A. eXtensible Markup Language",
    options: [
    "A. eXtensible Markup Language",
    "B. eXecutable Multiple Language",
    "C. eXTra Multi-Program Language",
    "D. eXamine Multiple Language"
    ]
  },
  
   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the size of int variable?",
    answer: "C. 32 bit",
    options: [
    "A. 8 bit",
    "B. 64 bit",
    "C. 32 bit",
    "D. 16 bit"
   ]
   },

   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "When static binding occurs?",
    answer: "B. Static binding occurs during Compile time.",
    options: [
    "A. Static binding occurs during load time.",
    "B. Static binding occurs during Compile time.",
    "C. Static binding occurs during run time",
    "D. None of the above."
   ]
   },

   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What happens when thread's sleep() method is called?",
    answer: "A. Thread returns to the waiting state.",
    options: [
    "A. Thread returns to the waiting state.",
    "B. Thread returns to the steady state.",
    "C. Thread starts running.",
    "D. None of the above."
   ]
   },

   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is false about String?",
    answer: "C. String is a primary data type.",
    options: [
    "A. String is immutable",
    "B. String can be created using new operator.",
    "C. String is a primary data type.",
    "D. None of the above."
   ]
   },
];